"To enjoy good health, to bring true happiness to one's family, to bring peace to all, one must first discipline and control one's own mind. If a man can control his mind he can find the way to Enlightenment, and all wisdom and virtue will naturally come to him.","Buddha"
"Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment.","Buddha"
"Thousands of candles can be lighted from a single candle, and the life of the candle will not be shortened. Happiness never decreases by being shared.","Buddha"
"To keep the body in good health is a duty... otherwise we shall not be able to keep our mind strong and clear.","Buddha"
"We are shaped by our thoughts; we become what we think. When the mind is pure, joy follows like a shadow that never leaves.","Buddha"
"Health is the greatest gift, contentment the greatest wealth, faithfulness the best relationship.","Buddha"
"No one saves us but ourselves. No one can and no one may. We ourselves must walk the path.","Buddha"
"Just as a candle cannot burn without fire, men cannot live without a spiritual life.","Buddha"
"It is better to conquer yourself than to win a thousand battles. Then the victory is yours. It cannot be taken from you, not by angels or by demons, heaven or hell.","Buddha"
"Three things cannot be long hidden: the sun, the moon, and the truth.","Buddha"
"You can search throughout the entire universe for someone who is more deserving of your love and affection than you are yourself, and that person is not to be found anywhere. You yourself, as much as anybody in the entire universe deserve your love and affection.","Buddha"
"Holding on to anger is like grasping a hot coal with the intent of throwing it at someone else; you are the one who gets burned.","Buddha"
"Just as treasures are uncovered from the earth, so virtue appears from good deeds, and wisdom appears from a pure and peaceful mind. To walk safely through the maze of human life, one needs the light of wisdom and the guidance of virtue.","Buddha"
"Whatever words we utter should be chosen with care for people will hear them and be influenced by them for good or ill.","Buddha"
"There are only two mistakes one can make along the road to truth; not going all the way, and not starting.","Buddha"
"However many holy words you read, however many you speak, what good will they do you if you do not act on upon them?","Buddha"
"We are what we think. All that we are arises with our thoughts. With our thoughts, we make the world.","Buddha"
"What we think, we become.","Buddha"
"You will not be punished for your anger, you will be punished by your anger.","Buddha"
"Do not overrate what you have received, nor envy others. He who envies others does not obtain peace of mind.","Buddha"
"With fools, there is no companionship. Rather than to live with men who are selfish, vain, quarrelsome, and obstinate, let a man walk alone.","Buddha"
"You, yourself, as much as anybody in the entire universe, deserve your love and affection.","Buddha"
"Work out your own salvation. Do not depend on others.","Buddha"
"The mind is everything. What you think you become.","Buddha"
"Peace comes from within. Do not seek it without.","Buddha"
"I never see what has been done; I only see what remains to be done.","Buddha"

