"Do the difficult things while they are easy and do the great things while they are small. A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step.","Lao Tzu"
"Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage.","Lao Tzu"
"Nature does not hurry, yet everything is accomplished.","Lao Tzu"
"A leader is best when people barely know he exists, when his work is done, his aim fulfilled, they will say: we did it ourselves.","Lao Tzu"
"Kindness in words creates confidence. Kindness in thinking creates profoundness. Kindness in giving creates love.","Lao Tzu"
"The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step.","Lao Tzu"
"Life is a series of natural and spontaneous changes. Don't resist them - that only creates sorrow. Let reality be reality. Let things flow naturally forward in whatever way they like.","Lao Tzu"
"I have just three things to teach: simplicity, patience, compassion. These three are your greatest treasures.","Lao Tzu"
"Life and death are one thread, the same line viewed from different sides.","Lao Tzu"
"In dwelling, live close to the ground. In thinking, keep to the simple. In conflict, be fair and generous. In governing, don't try to control. In work, do what you enjoy. In family life, be completely present.","Lao Tzu"
"Silence is a source of great strength.","Lao Tzu"
"Be content with what you have; rejoice in the way things are. When you realize there is nothing lacking, the whole world belongs to you.","Lao Tzu"
"Nothing is softer or more flexible than water, yet nothing can resist it.","Lao Tzu"
"If you do not change direction, you may end up where you are heading.","Lao Tzu"
"Mastering others is strength. Mastering yourself is true power.","Lao Tzu"
"To the mind that is still, the whole universe surrenders.","Lao Tzu"
"The key to growth is the introduction of higher dimensions of consciousness into our awareness.","Lao Tzu"
"Treat those who are good with goodness, and also treat those who are not good with goodness. Thus goodness is attained. Be honest to those who are honest, and be also honest to those who are not honest. Thus honesty is attained.","Lao Tzu"
"If you realize that all things change, there is nothing you will try to hold on to. If you are not afraid of dying, there is nothing you cannot achieve.","Lao Tzu"
"There was something undifferentiated and yet complete, which existed before Heaven and Earth. Soundless and formless, it depends on nothing and does not change. It operates everywhere and is free from danger. It may be considered the mother of the universe. I do not know its name; I call it Tao.","Lao Tzu"
"When the best leader's work is done the people say, 'We did it ourselves.'","Lao Tzu"
"When you are content to be simply yourself and don't compare or compete, everybody will respect you.","Lao Tzu"
"Health is the greatest possession. Contentment is the greatest treasure. Confidence is the greatest friend. Non-being is the greatest joy.","Lao Tzu"
"When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be.","Lao Tzu"
"Truthful words are not beautiful; beautiful words are not truthful. Good words are not persuasive; persuasive words are not good.","Lao Tzu"
"Love is of all passions the strongest, for it attacks simultaneously the head, the heart and the senses.","Lao Tzu"

