"Keep your thoughts positive because your thoughts become your words. Keep your words positive because your words become your behavior. Keep your behavior positive because your behavior becomes your habits. Keep your habits positive because your habits become your values. Keep your values positive because your values become your destiny.","Mahatma Gandhi"
"You can't change how people treat you or what they say about you. All you can do is change how you react to it.","Nicky Gumbel"
"Every day may not be good... but there's something good in every day","Alice Morse Earle"
"The POSITIVE THINKER sees the INVISIBLE, feels the INTANGIBLE, and achieves the IMPOSSIBLE.","Winston Churchill"
"Keep your face always toward the sunshine - and shadows will fall behind you.","Walt Whitman"
"The way to happiness: Keep your heart free from hate, your mind from worry. Live simply, expect little, give much. Scatter sunshine, forget self, think of others. Try this for a week and you will be surprised.","Norman Vincent Peale"
"The best thing to give to your enemy is forgiveness; to an opponent, tolerance; to a friend, your heart; to your child, a good example; to a father, deference; to your mother, conduct that will make her proud of you; to yourself, respect; to all others, charity.","Benjamin Franklin"
"Once you replace negative thoughts with positive ones, you'll start having positive results.","Willie Nelson"
"I will not let anyone walk through my mind with their dirty feet.","Mahatma Gandhi"
"Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time.","Thomas A. Edison"
"Faith is taking the first step even when you don't see the whole staircase.","Martin Luther King, Jr."
"I will love the light for it shows me the way, yet I will endure the darkness because it shows me the stars.","Og Mandino"
"With everything that has happened to you, you can either feel sorry for yourself or treat what has happened as a gift. Everything is either an opportunity to grow or an obstacle to keep you from growing. You get to choose.","Wayne Dyer"
"In times of great stress or adversity, it's always best to keep busy, to plow your anger and your energy into something positive.","Lee Iacocca"
"I am not afraid of tomorrow, for I have seen yesterday and I love today.","William Allen White"
"When you arise in the morning, think of what a precious privilege it is to be alive - to breathe, to think, to enjoy, to love.","Marcus Aurelius"
"Ability is what you're capable of doing. Motivation determines what you do. Attitude determines how well you do it.","Lou Holtz"
"Take chances, make mistakes. That's how you grow. Pain nourishes your courage. You have to fail in order to practice being brave.","Mary Tyler Moore"
"In the middle of every difficulty lies opportunity.","Albert Einstein"
"Just remember, you can do anything you set your mind to, but it takes action, perseverance, and facing your fears.","Gillian Anderson"
"When one door closes, another opens; but we often look so long and so regretfully upon the closed door that we do not see the one which has opened for us.","Alexander Graham Bell"
"Optimism is a happiness magnet. If you stay positive, good things and good people will be drawn to you.","Mary Lou Retton"
"When you can?t change the direction of the wind ? adjust your sails","H. Jackson Brown, Jr."
"If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything.","Malcolm X"
"When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it.","Henry Ford"
